<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Elden Ring on TheDoubleKill — Gaming News Template</title>
    <link>/tags/elden-ring/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Elden Ring on TheDoubleKill — Gaming News Template</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 10:00:00 +0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="/tags/elden-ring/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Elden Ring Nightreign Update 1.03 Out Now Ahead of The Forsaken Hollows DLC</title>
      <link>/posts/elden-ring-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 23 Dec 2025 10:00:00 +0600</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/elden-ring-update/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;From Software has just released the highly anticipated update 1.03 for Elden Ring, preparing the grounds for the upcoming Forsaken Hollows DLC. This update brings significant balance changes, performance improvements, and a few surprises for tarnished warriors.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;patch-notes-highlights&#34;&gt;Patch Notes Highlights&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Weapon Balancing:&lt;/strong&gt; Rivers of Blood has seen a slight adjustment (again), making it more viable in PvE but less oppressive in PvP.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Performance:&lt;/strong&gt; Fixed stuttering issues in the Lake of Rot area on PC.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;New Quest Steps:&lt;/strong&gt; Added new dialogue lines for NPC Jar Bairn.&lt;/li&gt;&#xA;&lt;/ul&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The community is already digging into the files to see if there are any hidden secrets leading into the &lt;em&gt;Forsaken Hollows&lt;/em&gt;. Stay tuned for our full breakdown of the DLC when it launches next week.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Elden Ring Nightreign 1.03 Update Ahead of Forsaken Hollows</title>
      <link>/posts/elden-ring-nightreign-patch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 03 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>/posts/elden-ring-nightreign-patch/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The new patch introduces balance changes, fixes, and improvements as players prepare for the upcoming DLC release.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
